[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
Ugh! It's so hot!
[MISCHIEVOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[MISCHIEVOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [COMICAL STING]
- [BOTH GASP]
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry!
You're making me thirsty--
I-I mean, I'm thirsty!
You're so hot--
I mean,
you're so hot to watch--
Whoo! It's so hot!
- It's really hot, isn't it?!
- S-Sorry, sorry.
That just caught me off guard.
- [JUNE] Yes.
- Yeah, it is hot.
- [JUNE] It's hot, isn't it?
- I'm going to grab some water.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I-It's hot, isn't it?
Is the A/C broken in your room?
[HUFFS] N-No.
I just don't turn it on.
Well, it's there
for you to use it.
Just because I have one
doesn't mean I have to use it.
Right?
Okay, suit yourself.
It's especially hot these days.
You'll get dehydrated.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[WATER POURING]
Yeah, you're right.
It's really hot.
[MISCHIEVOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you hungry?
- There's food over there.
- [CHUCKLING]
No!
I'm good.
Hmm!
I'm heading back to my room.
Good night.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[COMICAL STING]
[JUNE] O-M-G!
[SLURPS]
[LOUD GULPING]